<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Electronics on ctm.maloneylights.com</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/electronics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Electronics on ctm.maloneylights.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 23:08:58 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/electronics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ATX Adapter board</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/electronics/atxadapterboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 23:08:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/electronics/atxadapterboard/</guid>
      <description>This board was created to make a workbench power supply from an old computer power supply. There are many sites out there that have instructions on how to modify a power supply to convert it to a bench supply but most of them require you to open up the power supply to make the modifications. I wanted something that I could simply plug in and go. This also will allow me to quickly change power supplies in the event that it goes bad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renard Servo Controller</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/electronics/renardservocontroller/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 23:08:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/electronics/renardservocontroller/</guid>
      <description>The Renard Servo controller was designed to be able to control hobby servos in line with my Renard controllers. It ‘speaks’ the Renard protocol so it can be placed directly in line with other Renard controllers. The board was created in ExpressPCB and was designed to be self etchable(if that’s a word). I’ve included all the ExpressPCB files in the download.&#xA;The Servo SSR Replacement board </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Servo SSR Replacement board</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/electronics/servossrreplacementboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 23:08:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/electronics/servossrreplacementboard/</guid>
      <description>The SSSRR was created for controlling hobby servos using Renard Controllers that use external SSR’s. I chose to add isolation to the board. While this is probably overkill, it’s really a better way to do it.&#xA;The project was designed in ExpressPCB and I tried to make it easily self etchable. All PCB files are included in the download.&#xA;The Servo SSR Replacement board </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renard 8 DC</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/electronics/renard8dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 23:45:13 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/electronics/renard8dc/</guid>
      <description>This is my version of the Renard 8 origionally designed by Phil Short. This version is strictly for DC control. I added provisions for AC use but they have not been tested and I believe they will not work. The pcb files were created using ExpressPCB.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
